前情提要
Previously...
诺维奇伯爵
Count Nowicki.
- 诺维奇收到消息了 - 是的，当然
- Nowicki got the message. - Yes, of course.
我没想到伯爵会那样做
I didn't expect a count to behave like that.
- 真的?-为什么穆斯塔法要杀诺维奇？
- Really? - And why did Mustapha kill Nowicki?
因为诺维奇可能是个纳粹间谍
Because Nowicki was probably a Nazi spy.
纳粹最不想看到的就是
And the last thing the Nazis want
就是国王承认苏联主权
is for the King to recognize the Soviet Union.
我需要你帮我给拉贾奇基设套
I need you to set up Rajachki for me.
为什么？
Why?
我们说过: “不问任何问题”
We said: "No questions asked".
拉贾奇基被杀了
Rajachki was killed.
好像有人知道我们在准备什么..
As if someone knows what we are preparing...
共产国际突然对我们的组织产生了兴趣
The Comintern suddenly began to take an interest in our organization.
因为暗杀国王的计划已经开始了
Because the assassination of the king is being planned.
你的工作是控制住IMRO
Your job is just to keep IMRO under control.
并且做好准备
And to be ready.
你知道帕维里奇和保加利亚的联络人是谁吗？
Do you know who connects Pavelich with the Bulgarians?
安特 · 戈迪纳
Ante Godina.
一项新的行动正在准备之中
A new action is being prepared.
暗杀行动将在贝尔格莱德进行？
The assassination will be in Belgrade?
巨大的变化正在到来
Big changes are coming.
让日瓦科维奇自生自灭吧
Leave Zhivkovich to his fate.
是你把我扯进来的
You got me involved in this.
如果他们审问我，一定也会来找你
If they interrogate me, they'll come to you.
我和这件事一点关系也没有
I have nothing to do with it.
这是你的刺刀吗？
Is this your bayonet?
维多杰先生和他的妻子索尼娅就是被它杀死的
Mr. Vidoje and his wife Sonya were killed with it.
就是他，愿蛇把他的眼睛挖出来！
That's him, may the snake take his eyes out!
你看不出有人在陷害他吗？
You can't see someone set him up?
这一切都与阿皮斯和黑手党有关
This is related to Apis. And the Black Hand.
当阿皮斯和他的军官们被指控叛国罪时
When Apis and the officers were accused of high treason,
巴里亚克塔列维奇、法官、维多杰... 他们都参与其中
Baryaktarevich, the judge, Vidoje... Everyone was part of it.
当你检查拉贾奇基的文件时
When you start checking Rajachki's papers,
注意他和奥布拉德·萨夫科维奇
pay attention to how and how much he cooperated
是怎么合作的，有多少金额
with Obrad Savkovich.
我需要你的人
I need some of your men.
他现在还活着
He's alive. For now.
你知道该怎么做
You know what to do.
我有罪
I'm guilty.
我就是凶手
I am the killer.
哦，我的好警官！
Oh, my captain!
这次你来我家了
This time you came to my place.
但我看到你手里又拿着枪
But I see you have a gun in your hand again.
这算什么礼节
Except it's not etiquette,
你吓到这个小女孩了
you scared this little girl.
如果我不欠你的，那你现在就有麻烦了
If I didn't owe you, you'd be in trouble now.
别说废话了
Stop that bullshit.
别装傻，我会打爆你的头
Don't play dumb, I'll blow your brains out.
告诉我你要干嘛，别再威胁我了
Tell me what you have and stop threatening me,
因为我不会独自离开这个世界，这是肯定的
because I won't leave this world alone, that's for sure.
坐下！
Sit down!
我知道你是个杀人犯..
I knew you were a murderer...
但我不知道你还杀害无辜的女人
But I didn't know you were killing innocent women.
什么女人? ！
What women?!
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
我说的是我的索尼娅
I'm talking about my Sonya.
什么? ！
What?!
你不能就只杀维多杰..
You couldn't just kill Vidoje...
你还得杀了她！
You had to take her life, too!
仔细听我说..
Listen to me carefully...
我没杀那个人
I didn't kill that shit.
而且现在我知道了你有多爱他的妻子
And now that I see how much you loved his wife,
对不起，我没有杀他
I'm sorry I didn't kill him.
因为如果是我
Because if I did,
你的索尼娅现在就会健康地活着
your Sonya would be alive and healthy now.
我向你保证
I assure you of that.
你没有杀其他人？
And you didn't kill the others?
这是我的工作
That's my job.
我不杀那些罪有应得的人
I don't kill those who deserve it,
而是杀那些需要被杀的人
but those who need to be killed.
你没有杀拉贾奇基和诺维奇？
You didn't kill Rajachki and Nowicki?
既然我们敞开心扉
Since we're opening our hearts,
我跟你说实话
I'll be honest with you.
拉雅其奇算是侥幸逃过一劫
Rajachki narrowly escaped me...
但诺维奇确实是我杀的
And I killed Nowicki.
因为他准备暗杀国王
Because he was preparing to assassinate the king.
干得好，我亲爱的警官！
Great job, my dear captain!
我一直在说你应该当牧师
I've been saying for a long time that you should be a minister.
穆斯塔法 · 戈卢布奇什么时候开始保护亚历山大国王了？
Since when does Mustapha Golubich protect King Alexander?
我告诉过你，不是因为他值得，而是因为命令
I told you. Not by merit, but by order.
趁你还拿着枪我再告诉你一件事
I'll tell you one more thing, while you're still holding the gun.
这样就不会显得我只是在能吹牛的时候才吹牛
So that it doesn't turn out that I brag only when I can.
如果因为我刚才告诉你的事有什么问题
If there's a problem because of what I've just told you,
无论你躲到哪里，我都会找到你
I'll find you wherever you hide.
把枪放下
Put that gun down now,
因为我快没有耐心了
because my patience doesn't last forever.
巴尔干半岛的阴影 第二季 第七集
BLACK SUN SEASON 2 EPISODE 07
到了我这个年纪，就变得有耐心了
At my age, a person learns to have patience.
而且有远见
And to evaluate things from a distance.
这很明智
That's wise.
不幸的是，明智是当今社会的弱点
Unfortunately, wisdom is a weakness nowadays.
我越来越不理解当下了
I can understand the present less and less.
谁不是呢
Well, you're not the only one.
当合适的时机到来时，必须采取行动
When the right moment comes, action is necessary.
不能再等了
And it can't wait.
也许这就是你来贝尔格莱德的原因
Probably that's why you came to Belgrade.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
一定是很重要的事
It must be something very important,
因为没人通知我
because no one informed me.
我没有告诉任何人我要来
I didn't announce my arrival to anyone.
你不必觉得每件事都有阴谋
You don't have to see a conspiracy in everything.
我们的分舵有麻烦了
Our detachment is in big trouble here,
有些事情一定要做
and that requires certain actions.
我想这些事都不是我能参与的吧？
I guess those are actions I won't be involved in?
我们的兄弟像狗一样死去
Our brothers are dying like dogs
而你却什么都没做
and you've done nothing about it.
但我会的
But I will.
当我做了决定之后，会让你知道的
And I'll involve you in it, when I decide.
很高兴见到你
It was my pleasure.
回头见
See you soon.
等不及了！
Can't wait!
- 干杯 - 干杯！
- Cheers! - Cheers!
听着..
Listen...
你有没有告诉你朋友我和她的事？
You didn't tell your friend about her and me?
我没有
I didn't.
这不关我的事
That's none of my business.
别碰他
Don't touch him.
我不会的，长官
I won't, captain.
那个...凶手...
The one... who's killing...
他在杀害那些在萨洛尼卡审判中
He's killing those who fucked up
陷害你和你朋友阿皮斯的人
you and your pal Apis in the Thessaloniki process.
什么? ！
What?!
法官篡改了起诉书
The judge changed the indictment,
维多杰作了伪证
Vidoje gave false testimony,
巴雅克塔维奇是刽子手
Baryaktarevich was the executor...
我唯一不确定的是拉贾奇基做了什么
the only thing I don't know is what Rajachki did.
他在整个战争期间与奥地利人私下勾结
He was a link with the Austrians throughout the war.
他转达了奥地利的最后通牒，要搞垮我们
He conveyed the Austrian ultimatum to fuck us up.
你把这些事情都串起来了
You connected it well.
我唯一还没搞清楚的是凶手是谁
The only thing I still haven't figured out is who's killing.
如果不是你
If it's not you,
那有可能是
it's probably someone
以前黑手党的人
from your former organization, the Black Hand.
已经没有人了，塔纳西耶维奇
There's no one left, Tanasiyevich.
要么被杀要么被驱逐
Aca either killed us or expelled us.
不是我们做的
It's none of us.
不管是谁，都应该为他建造一座纪念碑
Whoever it is, a monument should be built for what it does.
已经建好了
It's already built.
是一个无名英雄纪念碑
He signs himself as an unknown hero.
你看，塞尔维亚还是有希望的
There you go. There's some hope for Serbia.
干杯！
Cheers!
在阿皮斯名单的最后是国王
At the end of your and Apis' list was the king.
也许在凶手的名单的最后也是国王，也许这是有关联的
Maybe there's a king at the end of his list, maybe it's connected.
国王不是我们名单上最后一个
It's not at the end of ours...
虽然我们可能会在名单上找到他
though we'd probably get to him.
但是在结束之前名单上肯定还有一个人
But there's one before the end, for sure.
佩塔尔 · 日瓦科维奇
Petar Zhivkovich.
没错，佩塔尔 · 日瓦科维奇
That's right. Petar Zhivkovich.
但话又说回来...
But then again...
如果纳粹准备暗杀国王
If the Nazis are preparing to assassinate the king,
他们和萨洛尼卡审判有什么关系？
what do they have to do with the Thessaloniki process?
这逻辑不通，真的
There's no logic, really.
新时代已经骚扰了日瓦科维奇好几天了
The New Age has been harassing Zhivkovich for days.
他们把他和诺维奇的谋杀案联系起来
They link him to Nowicki's murder.
这是真的
It's true.
我们杀了他，他们攻击了佩塔尔
We killed him, and they attacked Petar.
这里面有点东西...
There's something in that...
每次跟聪明人聊天
You see, every time you talk to smart people,
都会学到些什么
you get something.
你去查查塞尔维亚的戈培尔
You check the Serbian Goebbels,
他做任何事都不是没有目的的
he doesn't do anything by accident,
等我完成任务回来
and when I come back from the road,
看你能查到些什么
we'll see how far you've come.
干杯！
Cheers!
这些都是皮外伤，别担心，会愈合的
These are superficial wounds. Don't worry, they will heal.
你这警察的表情是在开玩笑吗? ！
Are you kidding me with those cop expressions?!
他不是第一个打我的人
He's not the first one who beat me in my life.
我小时候被打过，但这次...
I was beaten as a child, but this...
他完全疯了
He totally went crazy.
好像他以前是正常人一样
As if he was normal before.
他认为每个人都背叛了他
He thinks everyone betrayed him.
他甚至认为将军出卖了他
He even thinks the general sold him down the river.
完全疯了，他想和所有人开战
Fully went wild, he wants to start a war with everyone.
找个地方躲一躲怎么样？
How about getting away?
你认为这个镇上有个洞
You think there's a hole in this town
钻进去就能躲避修道士？
where you can hide from the Monk?
狗娘养的！
Motherfucker!
那离开这个城市呢？
Maybe disappear from the city?
走吧
Leave.
离开？
Leave?
暂时的
Temporarily.
我以后会处理的
I'll take care of it later.
我会保护你
And I'll protect you.
你会保护我？
You'll protect me?
还能有谁？
Who else?
你以为我想逃离修道士吗？
You think I want to run away from the Monk?
那你想怎么样？
Well, what do you want?
不能逃避像他这样的人
You can't run away from people like him.
只能杀了他
You can only kill them.
你终于发出去了吗？
Did you finally send it?
好像你是现学写字一样
As if you were carrying it on foot to Split.
你不能向贝尔格莱德的任何人解释任何事情
You can't explain anything to anyone in Belgrade.
他们说明天就到
They said it would arrive tomorrow.
这没有用
There's no use of that.
这可不妙，尼古拉
This is not good, Nikola.
放松点，米伦
Take it easy, Milun.
丹尼洛知道自己在做什么
Danilo knows what he's doing.
闭嘴，我们四面受敌
Shut up, we are attacked from all sides.
萨夫科维奇！
Oh, Savkovich!
你是来还我钱的？
You came to give me my money back?
告诉你兄弟我要见他
Tell your brother I want to see him.
他为什么会想见你？
Why do you think he wants to see you?
我有个提议
I have a proposal for him.
为了节省你的时间，你的提议被拒绝了
Well, to save you time, it's rejected.
幸运的是，你哥哥不会那么傻
Fortunately, your brother is not such a fool.
告诉他我的提议不应该被拒绝
Tell him my proposal shouldn't be rejected.
我们走！
Let's go!
我要走了
I'm leaving.
好吧
Okay.
你不问我去哪里吗？
You won't ask me where?
反正你也不会告诉我真相
You wouldn't tell me the truth anyway.
你甚至不祝我一路平安？
You won't even wish me a safe journey?
一路平安
Have a safe journey.
博雅纳！
Boyana!
怎么把你弄进警局? ，还要弄进牢房? ！
How to get you into Glavnjacha? To the cells?!
你都能把妓女带进去，却不能带我去? ！
You could have brought whores there, but you can't get me in?!
拜托！
Oh, come on!
你是前任探长
You're a former inspector
现在你要我带你去见
whom I need to take to the former chief
因涉嫌谋杀被捕的前任警长
who's been arrested for murder.
未经证实的谋杀
Unproven murder.
他认罪了，塔尼
He confessed, Tane.
他说了”我是凶手”？
That's exactly what he said, "I am the killer"?
他给他儿子打了电话..
He called his son and...
然后就认罪了
Then he confessed to everything.
他给他儿子打电话了？
He called his son?
斯特拉辛加？
Strahinja?
吃的来了！
Here's the food!
还有白兰地！
And the brandy!
给你！
Here you are!
日沃因，老实告诉我
Zhivoyin, tell me honestly.
你认为他有罪吗？
Do you think he's guilty?
这不是我该思考的问题，我只是个小警察
It's not my place to think, I'm just a gendarme.
不，你是他的朋友
No, you're his friend.
如果迪米特里耶维奇有可能是无辜的
If there is any chance that Dimitriyevich is innocent,
我可以证明！
I can prove it!
我只是想见见他，和他谈谈！
I just need to see him, to talk to him!
好吧
Well...
如果迪米特里耶维奇最后被绞死
If Dimitriyevich ends up hanged,
结果证明他是无罪的
and it turns out that he's not guilty
而你本可以帮助他
and that you could have helped him,
到时候你再说
then try to explain yourself
你只是个普通的小警察
that you're just an ordinary gendarme.
塔尼，你真是不可理喻
Tane, you're impossible to deal with.
你们马其顿的工厂被摧毁只是时间问题
It's a matter of time before your plants in Macedonia are destroyed.
工人将会被驱逐，货物也将被烧毁
People will be eliminated and the goods burned.
你的海洛因生意结束了
Your heroin job is over.
什么都没有结束
Nothing is over.
对于如何从这一切中获得胜利，我有一个建议
I have a suggestion on how to emerge victorious from all this.
我听着呢
I'm listening.
我给你一份生意
I offer you a share in the business,
国家的保护和海洛因分销的安全路线
state protection and safe routes for the distribution of heroin.
时代在变化
Times are changing.
我们需要新的人，有抱负的人
We need new people, ambitious.
我在你身上看到了
I see that in you.
我的搭档是米里奇先生
My partner is Mr. Mirich,
顺便说一句，你要和他和解
with whom you'll reconcile, by the way.
暂时
Temporarily.
他杀了我弟弟
He killed my brother.
- 我无法释怀 - 你不必这样
- I can't get over it. - You don't have to.
米里奇不适合这份工作
Mirich has become bad for this job,
早晚有一天他会消失
his dismissal is inevitable.
但是目前，他还是有用的
But for now, he's still useful.
怎么说？
So?
我很高兴，还有一件事
I'm very glad. And one more thing.
我需要你的帮助
I need one of your services.
安德拉 · 塔纳西耶维奇
Andra Tanasiyevich...
前任探长，我想你应该认识他...
The former inspector, I think you know him...
你必须杀了他
You have to kill him.
你找谁？
What do you need?
我在找阿列克西奇先生
I'm looking for Mr. Aleksich.
我想他的名字是斯蒂芬
I think his name is Stephan.
让我看看
Let me check.
把枪放下，否则我打爆他的头！
Drop that gun or I'll spill his brains!
什么事？
Yes?
我有些消息，老板
I have some news, boss.
如果是好消息，对你来说会更好
It would be better for you if it was good.
我觉得挺好的
I think it's good.
我听着呢
I'm listening.
我们收到来自贫民窟的情报
We've got an alert from the Yataghan slum.
大多数人都离开了
Most of the men left.
不会吧! 真的吗？
No way! Really?
猪跑了？
The pigs ran away?
就像我说的，男人大多离开了
Like I said, the men left,
只留下女人和孩子
leaving only women and children.
看来我的老朋友米兰没那么蠢...
Looks like my old friend Milan isn't that stupid...
或者他是真蠢？
Or maybe he is?
我们走着瞧
We'll see.
我们接下来该做什么？
What should we do next?
我们会派宪兵队过去
We'll send the gendarmerie
还有拿着镐头的囚犯，让他们去打砸抢烧
and prisoners with picks to break and clean everything
这将是最终的解决方案
and that will be the final solution.
召集我的人吗，一起去帮忙？
To gather my people, to help?
不..
No...
不
No.
你现在要去马其顿
You're now going to Macedonia,
实施另一个最终解决方案
to implement another final solution.
你联系当地警方
You'll contact the local authorities,
他们会告诉你基拉老板的藏身之处
they'll give you the exact location of the Boss Kyro's hideout.
你将提供所有的后勤支持和必要的协助..
You'll provide all the logistics and necessary assistance...
然后你就去打马其顿黑帮
and then you'll strike at that Macedonian gang...
狠狠打
Strongly.
等你打完了..
And when you're done with them...
确保一切都结束了，我要去短途旅行
We'll be sure it's over. I'm going on a short trip.
在我回来之前把事情做好
Finish it until I get back.
保加利亚边境 马其顿 德拉切村
Dramche village, Macedonia, Bulgaria border
上帝啊！
Jesus Christ!
有人要把这个注入他们的血管? ！
They're going to put this in their veins?!
我能说什么呢？
What can I say?
我选择了把灵魂出卖给魔鬼的感觉
I choose the feeling of selling my soul to the devil.
哦不! 别担心！
Oh, no! Don't worry!
这个比鸦片贵三倍
This is three times more expensive than opium.
我们来谈点正经事
We'll make some serious business.
这工作...
This is a hell of a job...
意味着这工作不错
Which means it's good.
我不喜欢，闻起来像死人
I don't like it. It smells like death.
只有这样才能伤到修道士
It's the only way to reach the Monk.
如果黑山发展运输
If the Montenegrin develops the transport,
六个月后他就完蛋了
he'll be fucked up in six months.
- 我等不及那天了 - 女儿！
- I can't wait for that day. - Daughter!
也许你可以等待那一天
You may wait for that day,
但我不能回布科沃了
but I won't be able to come back to Bukovo.
我女儿在这里很无聊
And my daughter is bored here.
你需要增加产量
You need to increase production.
你必须再建一个工厂
You have to make another production plant.
- 你这么认为? - 我很确定
- You think? - I'm sure of it.
- 我们会帮你的 - 好了，我赢！
- We'll help you. - Okay, mine!
国王! 我的牌大
The king! I'm stronger.
不，王牌比国王更大！
No, the ace is stronger than the king!
- 不，国王才是 - 拜托！
- No, the king is. - Come on!
是个牧师，不是国王! 马其顿人没有国王
It's a priest, not the king! Macedonia doesn't have the king.
牧师就是马其顿的国王
Well, the priest is the king in Macedonia.
安琪说得对! 谁也别碰他！
Angelche is right! Don't anyone touch him!
安琪，你是实验室的技术员吗？
Angelche, are you the main lab technician here?
我的工作是喂猪，打断腿，但你说的那个工作我也可以这样做
I feed the pigs and break legs, but I can do that too.
好吧，让我们看看你怎么做
Okay, let's see how we're gonna do this.
安琪，告诉我我们需要什么...
Angelche, tell me what do we need...
他们在闲逛的时候，我们却在这里工作
While they're fucking around, we're working here.
每个人都有自己的工作
Everyone has their own job.
我们的工作是搬运
We're in charge of transportation.
这叫做等级制度
It's called hierarchy.
这叫做洗脑制度
It's called brain fucking.
嘿，小伙子们！
Hey, boys!
我看你们很辛苦
I see you're struggling.
想喝点水吗？
Want some water?
介绍一下你自己吧
It would be nice to introduce yourself.
斯坦尼斯拉夫，大家都叫我赞内
Stanislav. They call me Tzane.
别扯犊子，大家都叫你小钢炮
Don't bullshit, everyone calls you Diesel.
拿着这个！
Take this barrel!
我是雅娜
I'm Yana.
这不是水！
This is not water!
你不喜欢？
You don't like it?
小刚票，别调情了，赶紧搬
Diesel, stop flirting and start carrying barrels.
我听说你是个拳击手
Hey, I've heard you're a boxer.
我不喜欢恶霸
I don't like bullies...
只喜欢好人
Just nice guys.
拳击是一项高尚的技术
Boxing is a noble skill.
- 高尚个屁! 过来! - 闭嘴！
- Noble my ass! Come here! - Shut up!
我是亚塔汗贫民窟和枪支贫民窟的联赛冠军
I'm the champion of the Yataghan slum and the Gun slum.
不可能！
No way!
雅娜！
Yana!
回家去
Go home.
再见，冠军
See you, champion.
冠军，我们还有20桶
Champion, we have twenty barrels left.
根本没生意做
There's no business.
我都快忘了被干是什么感觉
I'll forget how it's done.
下面都变紧了
It'll be tight down there.
我的也是
Mine, too.
- 下午好 - 下午好！
- Good afternoon! - Good afternoon!
中尉，工作愉快！
Lieutenant, happy work!
塔尼，好久不见! 怎么了？
Tane, long time no see! What's up?
- 这是迪米特里耶维奇的儿子 - 斯特拉辛加
- This is Dimitriyevich's son. - Strahinja.
我是德拉吉尼亚，他被捕了？
Draginya. He's under arrest?
大家都知道了，是吧？
Everyone knows it, huh?
这里什么都知道
Everything is known here.
我们得把他藏起来一段时间
We need to hide him for a while.
好了，过来，快点！
Okay, come here. Come on!
你不会问为什么吗？
You won't ask why?
你的话对我来说足够了，如果你让我把他藏起来，我就把他藏起来
Your word is enough for me. If I have to hide him, I'll do it.
我的好中尉
That's my Draginya!
生活怎么样？
How's life? Huh?
他们把我儿子带到了马其顿
They took my boy to Macedonia.
我听说了
I heard that.
局势正在升温
The situation is heating up.
我一点也不喜欢
I don't like it, at all.
我不喜欢我的孩子离开我的视线
I don't like it when my child is out of sight.
嗯，斯特拉辛加现在就在你的视线范围内，所以你要好好照顾他
Well, Strahinja is now in your sight, so take care of him a bit.
别担心赞内，他会照顾好自己的
Don't worry about Tzane, he'll take care of himself.
谢谢！
Thanks, Draginya!
快点！
Come on!
孩子们，你们破案了！
Boys, you solved the case!
干得好! 恭喜！
Well done! Congratulations!
干杯！
Cheers!
警长先生
Mr. Chief,
这案子还远远没有破
this is far from a solved case.
告诉我，孩子，你是怎么忍受这个疯子的？
Tell me boy, how do you put up with this lunatic?
我同意督察的观点，我们离破案还很远
I agree with the Inspector that we're far from a solution.
真的吗？
Really?
那就去破案吧
Well, then go solve the case
滚出去！
and get the fuck out of here!
谢谢你的支持，但是没有必要
Thanks for the solidarity, but it wasn't necessary.
这是搭档该做的
That's what partners do.
我有一种感觉，我们一直都在错误的方向上
I have a feeling we're on the wrong track all the time.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
好像在这背后还有更强大更致命的东西
As if there's something much stronger and more fateful behind this
比纪念碑委员会和
than the fucking Committee for the construction of the monument
新的和解协议更重要
and the new settlement.
萨洛尼卡审判
The Thessaloniki process.
被杀的人都在其中扮演着模糊的角色
Everyone there had a murky role.
萨洛尼卡审判是...审判阿比斯？
The Thessaloniki process is... The thing against Apis?
审判黑手党
And against the Black Hand.
好像一切都比我们想象的要更具有针对性
As if everything is much more personal than we believed it was.
- 看起来像是报复 - 我不明白
- It seems like revenge. - I don't understand.
矿工巴雅克塔维奇是刽子手
Miner Baryaktarevich was in the firing squad.
凶手切下了他用来拔枪的食指
The killer cut off his index finger that he used to pull the weapon.
凶手挖出法官的眼睛
He dug the judge's eyes out.
是因为正义本应该是盲目的，但在这个案子中却并非如此
Justice should have been blind but in this case it wasn't.
凶手割掉了维多杰的舌头
He cut Vidoje's tongue
因为他作伪证
because he testified falsely.
一切都很合理
Everything fits.
我只需要调查一下拉贾奇基
I just have to check Rajachki
看看他和萨洛尼卡审判有什么关系
and find out what he has to do with the Thessaloniki process.
- 探长! - 什么事？
- Inspector! - Yes?
如果迪米特里耶维奇是故意设计这一切来误导我们呢？
What if Dimitriyevich set it all up just to mislead us?
他在警察局工作多年，他应该能做到
He worked in the police for years, he could have known that.
一切皆有可能
Anything is possible...
但我不相信
I don't believe it, though.
- 我什么都不明白 - 斯坦科！
- I don't understand anything. - Stanko!
你有访客
You have a visitor.
博雅纳！
Boyana!
你有时间谈谈吗？
Do you have some time to talk?
- 现在? - 是的
- Now? - Yes.
- 我还有工作要做... - 那好吧
- I have to finish something... - Oh, okay then.
嘿! 发生什么事了？
Hey! Anything happened?
不，我只是想问点事情
No, I just wanted to ask something.
如果你愿意的话，你今晚八点左右来找我
You can come over tonight, if you want. Around eight.
- 不，还是算了... - 拜托
- No, I didn't... - Please.
我来做晚饭
I'll make dinner.
- 好吧，八点? - 八点
- Okay. Eight? - Eight.
再见！
See you!
南斯拉夫王国 贝尔格莱德 保罗王子的住所
THE RESIDENCE OF PRINCE PAUL BELGRADE, KINGDOM OF YUGOSLAVIA
巴尔图已经确认了
Bartu has confirmed his arrival
他会来参加开工仪式
and he will attend the start of construction.
我希望你来管理这项工程
I would like you to take control of the works
尽可能地加快施工速度
and speed them up as much as possible.
另外，我希望你在访问期间组织安保工作
Also, I would like you to organize security during the visit.
我不会这个任务交给军队或警察
I would not leave it to the army or the police.
- 不好意思，我不想... - 我知道
- Excuse me, I would not... - I know.
我知道你是怎么看待拆除日尔诺夫的
I know what you think about the demolition of Zhrnov,
就当是国王殿下的
but take it as a personal request
个人请求吧
of His Royal Highness.
当然
Of course.
巴尔图将直接从莫斯科前往贝尔格莱德
Bartu will come to Belgrade directly from Moscow.
我才你们已经准备好了礼物？
With the final offer, I assume?
用红色蝴蝶结装饰着
Decorated with a red bow.
你的假设是... 错误的
Your assumption is... wrong.
国王将拒绝承认苏联主权
The king will refuse the recognition of the Soviet Union.
我知道这让你很开心，而且不仅是你
I know it makes you happy, and not only you,
我知道这个决定是值得尊敬的，但这会给我们带来新的敌人
and I know it may be honourable, but it will bring us new enemies.
好像我们敌人还不够多似的
As if we don't have enough of them already.
我们会挺过去的
We will endure it.
你这么认为？
You think so?
希望如此
I hope so.
不管怎样，恐怕我们很快就会知道答案了
Anyway, I'm afraid we'll find out very soon.
奥地利 维也纳
VIENNA, AUSTRIA
有人说巴尔干地区会被大雪覆盖
They say the Balkans are covered with snow.
暴风雪还在酝酿之中
The storm is still brewing.
你是谁，他们没告诉我你的事吗？
Who are you, they didn't tell me about you?
我是万乔的朋友，我叫波格丹·拉扎罗夫
Vancho's friend. My name is Bogdan Lazarov.
万乔让我来找你
Vancho sent me to you.
万乔给了我一份名单，上面没有你的名字
Vancho gave me a list, I don't remember your name.
肯定有的
It was there, for sure.
我要去洗手间
I have to go to the toilet.
你哪儿也不能去，我的朋友
You're not going anywhere, my friend.
没错
That's right.
乌斯塔莎，你他妈的在害怕什么? 看你的报！
Ustasha, what are you fucking afraid of? Read!
没错
That's right.
很好
Yeah, that's right.
你为谁工作？
Who do you work for?
让我来解释一下
Let me explain.
你没在任何名单上见过我，因为我不在这里
You haven't seen me on any list, because I'm not here.
但我看到你在皮塔尔 · 日瓦科维奇的薪水册上
But I saw you on Petar Zhivkovich's payroll.
如果你不想让你的上司知道
If you don't want your fucking superior to know
你在对付塞尔维亚警察
what you're dealing with Serbian cops,
你最好听我说
you better listen to me.
我听说有人背叛他的时候他会很凶
I've heard he can be nasty when someone betrays him.
我想尽快见到你上级
I want to meet the superior as soon as possible.
为什么？
Why?
有些信息只有他能告诉我
There's some information that only he can give me.
让他去那个你们这些法西斯
Get him to come to that club
常去的俱乐部
where fascists like you meet.
照我说的做，你就再也见不到我了
Do it and you'll never see me again.
- 听懂了吗? - 我们会去的
- Do we have a deal? - We'll be there.
好吧
All right.
我就想要这个
I'm counting on it.
如果你耍我，这将是你做的最后一件事
If you fuck me over, it'll be the last thing you do.
“为祖国做好准备!”
"Ready for the homeland!"
我得知道你是谁才能回应你的问候
I'd respond to your greeting if I knew who the fuck you were.
你很快就会知道的，安特
You'll find out soon, Ante.
你一定会知道的
You'll definitely find out.
我真的搞不懂
I really don't get this.
先生们！
Gentlemen!
抱歉我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
你知道这是怎么回事... 我工作很忙
You know how it is... I work a lot.
你在里面玩的时候
While you enjoyed there,
我们还挺喜欢看你的素描和画
we enjoyed watching your sketches and drawings a bit.
看起来你只喜欢草图和素描
It seems that you'll only enjoy the sketches and drawings,
因为不会有纪念碑
because there will be no monument.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
这需要很长时间吗? 我还有很多工作要做
Will this take long? I still have a lot of work to do.
我们是来通知你..
We have come to inform you that...
从现在开始，纪念碑的建造
from now on, the construction of the monument
在国王卫队的管辖之下
is under the jurisdiction of the King's Guard.
我应该为此感到高兴吗？
And I should be happy about it?
一批新的大理石将于下星期到达
A new delivery of marble will arrive next week
你就能继续工作了
and you'll be able to continue working.
之前已经到了一批，但是没有送到日尔诺夫
Deliveries have arrived before, but not to Zhrnov.
你想怎么样
What do you think about
才能结束这个玩笑? ！
ending this joke?!
我听着呢
I'm listening.
法国外交部长巴尔图
The Minister of Foreign Affairs of France, Bartu,
要来拜访我们的国王
is visiting our king.
他们两个将一起炸毁日尔诺夫
The two of them will, together, blow up Zhrnov.
这样你就可以在那
So that you can place...
建造你的这个奇迹
this miracle of yours there.
我们在这为你服务
We are here to make it possible for you.
不是因为你..
Not because of you...
而是因为这是我们国王的意愿
but because it is the wish of our king.
我说的够清楚了吗？
Do I make myself clear?
日沃因让你等他，他晚上会来
Zhivoyin told you to wait for him, he'll come in the evening.
我知道
I know.
你准备好干坏事了吗？
Are you getting ready to do some shit?
你在乎什么？
What do you care?
操，你什么都不告诉我
Fuck, a man can't tell you anything.
哦，漂亮妹妹来了！
Oh, here's our girl!
哇！
Wow!
这里又不太平了
There's gonna be some shit here.
好吧，我不打扰你了
Okay, I won't bother you.
我不是来吵架或和解的
I didn't come to quarrel or to reconcile.
我来是想告诉你一些你需要知道的事情
I came to tell you something I think you need to know.
告诉我
Tell me.
银行的文件到了
Papers from the bank also arrived.
你分析的很对，探长
You judged it well, inspector.
这座纪念碑的建造工程是洗钱的屏障
The construction of the monument is a screen for money laundering.
一场史无前例的盗窃
For the theft of unprecedented proportions.
他们要筹集资金在贫民窟建造住宅区
They are directing money to build that settlement in Yataghan slum.
那个协议..
That settlement...
那些是德国的工厂
Those are German industrial plants.
他们计划在巴尔干半岛中心建立一个纳粹基地
They are building a Nazi base in the centre of the Balkans.
这是对国家政权的打击
It's a blow against the state.
由国家资助的叛国罪
A treason financed by state money.
等等，我不明白
Wait, I don't get it.
- 一切都是有联系的! - 什么是有联系的？
- Everything is connected! - What is connected?
日尔诺夫大理石的盗窃，德国工厂
The theft of marble on Zhrnov, the construction of German plants,
购买矿井，还有失踪的克劳斯
the purchase of a mine, Klaus who disappeared
我一直没有他的消息
and I haven't heard from him,
玛丽亚 · 奥里奇突然来到贝尔格莱德
Maria Orsich suddenly comes to Belgrade,
诺维奇，拉贾奇基，阿里姆皮耶 · 米里奇...
Nowicki, Rajachki, Alimpiye Mirich...
而这一切的幕后黑手...
And the man behind everything...
奥布拉德 · 萨夫科维奇
Obrad Savkovich.
是的，他无处不在
Yes. He is everywhere.
他接管了生意...
He takes over the business, prepares the ground...
就等着皮塔尔 · 日瓦科维奇倒台
when Petar Zhivkovich falls, and that's a matter of days...
只有国王会幸存
Only the king will remain.
他们想毁掉一切
They want to destroy everything,
把他们的意识形态强加于人
to impose their ideology...
这才是国王必须死的原因
That's why the king must die.
奥里奇夫人
Mrs. Orsich.
- 萨夫科维奇先生 - 谢谢
- Mr. Savkovich. - Thanks.
你认为被人看到我们聊天是明智的吗？
Do you think it's smart to be seen together?
我没有隐瞒我的行踪
I'm not hiding my visit.
相反，我希望这能引起一些反应
On the contrary, I'd like it to provoke some reactions.
这样我们才能更好地理解这个混乱局面
That way we might better understand this mess.
我相信不会有任何反应
I don't believe there will be any reactions.
我必须承认我对你的到来感到惊讶
I must admit that I was surprised by your arrival.
这是必要的
It's necessary.
拉贾奇基被杀改变了一切
The murder of Rajachki changes everything.
什么都没有改变
It doesn't change anything.
我认为不是
I wouldn't agree.
一切都在按计划进行，亲爱的
Everything is going according to plan, my dear.
那是谁杀了他？
Well, then who killed him?
我们迟早会知道的
We'll find out sooner or later.
拉贾奇基偶尔也有点用...
Rajachki was occasionally useful...
但他是个白痴
But he was a fool.
他从来不是我们计划的一部分
He was never part of our plan.
拉贾奇基在被杀之前发现了一些重要的东西
Rajachki discovered something important before he was killed.
非常重要
Very important.
恐怕我们失去控制了
I'm afraid we're out of control.
先是诺维奇，现在是拉贾奇基...
First Nowicki, now Rajachki...
有人在盯着我们
Someone is following us.
即使是这样，我也看不出这事会造成什么影响
Even if that's the case, I don't see how it affects anything.
就连你也不知道细节
And even you don't know the details.
这正是我所担心的
That's what I'm afraid of.
那些乌斯塔沙的白痴跟你一样都在胡说八道
Well, those Ustasha idiots bragged just like you,
但他们把一切都搞砸了
but they messed up everything they could.
女士，他们和我有些不同..
Ma'am, there are some differences between them and me...
我不是白痴
I'm not an idiot.
诺维奇被杀确实令人担忧，但并不影响我们的计划
Nowicki's murder is worrying but it doesn't affect our plan.
他被杀那天本该告诉我的事
And what he was supposed to tell me the day he was killed,
我们现在知道了
we certainly know now.
巴尔图确认了他的来访
We know that Bartu confirmed his arrival.
我不需要告诉你
I don't need to tell you
我们有多在乎这次成功
how much we care about this being successful.
所以清除任何可能的阻碍是非常必要的..
That's why it's very important to remove all possible obstacles...
而且要及时
In time.
是的
Yes.
玛雅夫人告诉我一件很有趣的事
Mrs. Maya told me a very interesting thing.
她最近从共产国际的熟人那里得到消息
She recently received information from her acquaintances from the Comintern
有人在计划暗杀国王
that the assassination of the king was being planned.
真的吗？
Oh, really?
有意思
Interesting.
臭名昭著的穆斯塔法 · 戈卢布里奇告诉她的
The infamous Mustapha Golubich told her that.
- 你听说过他吗?-听说过
- Have you heard of him? - Yes, I have.
玛雅太太突然对拉贾奇基
Mrs. Maya is suddenly very interested
的生意产生了兴趣
in the business of our brother Rajachki.
因为这一切
Because of all this,
我很好奇诺维奇是否收到你的信息了
I wonder if Nowicki got your message at all.
萨夫科维奇先生，如果我没理解错的话
Mr. Savkovich, if I understood correctly,
你怀疑玛雅夫人有事瞒着我们？
you suspect that Mrs. Maya is hiding something from us?
我可没这么说
I didn't say that.
我只是和你分享新信息，仅此而已
I'm just sharing new information with you, that's all.
也许这并不意味着什么
Maybe it doesn't mean anything.
不管怎样，我来对付玛雅
Anyway, leave Mrs. Maya to me.
像以前一样
Like before.
爱情与美酒
Love and wine.
现在只剩酒了
Now just wine.
不用了，谢谢
No, I'm fine, thanks.
那么，酒也没有了
So, not even wine.
你想谈什么？
What did you want to talk about?
我是共产党员
I'm a member of the Communist Party.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
什么时候开始的？
Since when?
我在苏黎世的时候
Ever since I was in Zurich.
你为什么不告诉我？
Why didn't you tell me?
我怎么能告诉你呢？
How could I tell you that?
你会逮捕像我这样的人
You arrest people like me.
这就是从我们分手的时候开始的
So that was the beginning of our breakup.
不
No.
不，我们分手是从...
No, our breakup started when...
从你每天在妓院过夜的时候
You spent night shifts in brothels.
好吧
Okay.
任何一个妓女都能做到我做不到的事
And when every whore could do what I can't.
我们已经听说了！
We've already heard that!
是的
Yes.
我们以前也遇到过这种情况
We've been through this before.
你想谈什么？
What did you want to talk about?
我不能把一切都告诉你
I can't tell you everything.
我知道，党的阴谋
I know. The party conspiracy.
不..
No...
这不是个好主意
This wasn't a good idea.
等等...嘿！等等! 别走！
Wait... Wait. Hey, wait! Stop!
对不起
I'm sorry.
什么事在困扰你？
What's bothering you?
我卷入了..
I got involved in...
我得去个地方
I gotta go somewhere.
- 我得躲起来 - 有多危险？
- I have to hide. - How dangerous it is?
我不知道
I don't know.
你什么都不能告诉我吗？
Can't you tell me anything?
不能
No.
博雅纳，我... 我不明白你的意思
Boyana, I... I do not understand you.
你来找我
You came to me,
你告诉我你是共产党员
you told me that you are a member of the Communist Party...
我想帮你
I want to help you,
但你什么都不能告诉我...那你为什么要来找我? ！
and you can't tell me anything... Why did you come then?!
我无处可去了
I have nowhere to go.
好吧
Okay.
那这样
Here's how we'll do it.
你可以住在我家
You'll stay at my place.
不不
No, no...
这是警察的家，最安全的地方
This is a cop's home, it's the safest place.
你会有自己的房间
You'll have your own room.
怎么样
There you go.
谢谢你
Thank you.
好了
Come on.
一切都会好的
Everything will be fine.
相信我
Trust me.
安特！
Ante!
哦，你是..
Oh, mister...
拉扎洛夫
Lazarov.
哦对，请坐，喝一杯
Yes, sit down, have a drink, please.
高贵的先生..
Mr. Superior...
对不起，我们能私下谈谈吗？
Excuse me, can we talk in private?
可以，当然! 戈迪娜，走吧
Yes, of course! Godina, leave.
不用担心她，她什么都不懂
Don't worry about her, she doesn't understand.
亲爱的，请等一下
Honey, wait please.
拉扎洛夫先生
Mr. Lazarov,
我们的朋友万乔还好吗？
how's our friend Vancho?
还行
So-so.
过去几个月我们一直在等你的消息
The last few months we are waiting for news from you,
他失去了耐心，这对健康不利
and he loses patience, and it's not good for health,
特别紧张，如果你明白的话
especially for the nerves, if you understand.
不幸的是我们没有给万乔带来好消息
Unfortunately, we don't have very good news for our friend Vancho,
但我们也没有坏消息
but we don't have any bad news either.
这可不太好，什么消息都没有
Not easy, it's not good to go back to Vancho
就回去见万乔先生
and tell him I didn't find out anything.
告诉他我们就指望保加利亚的 IMRO 了
Tell him we're seriously counting on the Bulgarian IMRO.
高贵的先生
Mr. Superior,
我可以和你开诚布公地谈谈吗？
may I speak openly with you?
当然
Of course.
我们听说在贝尔格莱德策划了一次行动
We heard that an action was planned in Belgrade,
而这项行动你我双方都没有参与决策，这是真的吗？
without you and without us, is that true?
很明显我们暗杀塞尔维亚独裁者的计划
It's obvious that our plan to assassinate the Serbian dictator
只是众多计划之一
is just one of the plans.
至于贝尔格莱德，我们已经听说了，但那是无稽之谈
As for Belgrade, we've heard that, but that is nonsense.
我不认为那些塞尔维亚人会做什么
I doubt that some Serbs will do anything there.
但是让我们坚持对法国的计划
But let's stick to our plan with France.
法国？
France?
万乔什么都没告诉你吗？
Vancho didn't tell you anything?
不，我知道
No, no, I know, I know.
克劳斯先生，过来，请过来
Mr. Klaus, come, come please.
帕维里奇先生，我只是想简单地问候你一下
Mr. Pavelich, I just wanted to greet you briefly.
这是我的朋友
This is my friend.
- 拉扎洛夫 - 拉扎洛夫
- Lazarov. - Lazarov.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
请坐
Have a seat.
我们认识吗？
Do we know each other?
我不这么认为
I do not think so.
克劳斯，坐
Klaus, sit down.
对不起，我有很多工作要做
I have a lot of work to do, sorry.
我明天得早起
I have to get up early tomorrow.
就像我说的，我只是想简单地和你打个招呼
Like I said, I just wanted to say hello to you briefly.
当然
Of course.
不管怎么说，也没那么好
Anyway, it's not that good.
没有钱，意大利人耍了我们
There's no money, the Italians fucked us over.
没有我们这些朋友
Without these friends of ours,
我们的运动就会瓦解
our movement would have disintegrated.
唯一能让我们继续下去的就是
The only thing that still keeps us going is the idea
摆脱那个塞尔维亚暴君的想法
to get rid of that Serbian tyrant
一劳永逸地摆脱枷锁
and to get rid of those shackles once and for all.
戈迪纳先生
Mr. Godina,
那个坐在帕维里奇旁边自称是拉扎洛夫的人是谁？
who's the man who sits with Pavelich and claims to be Lazarov?
一切都会好的..
Everything will be fine...
对不起，先生,
Excuse me, Mr. Superior,
我要走了
I'm leaving now.
为什么? 还早呢
Why? It's still early.
对不起，这是我的荣幸
I'm sorry. It was my pleasure.
我知道，姑娘们一会就来了！
I know, but the girls will come!
- 再见 - 再见
- Good bye. - Good bye.
这个公寓很漂亮
This apartment is very beautiful.
很暖和
It's so warm
引人注目的暗色调
and interestingly dark...
就像你一样
Just like you.
是的
Yeah.
但我们不是来谈这个的，对吧？
But we're not here to talk about that, are we?
对不起，我只是好奇
Sorry, I'm just curious.
请坐
Have a seat, please.
事实上，直到现在我才明白我对你知之甚少
In fact, only now I see how little I know about you.
这样不好吗？
And that's bad?
这要看情况
It depends.
- 我想知道更多 - 为了更好控制我？
- I'd like to know more. - To control me easier?
为了更好地了解你，亲爱的
To get to know you better, my dear.
别紧张，这又不是听证会
Relax, you aren't at the hearing.
不是吗? 我可不这么认为
I'm not? It didn't look that way to me.
你错了
Well, you were wrong.
虽然我承认
Although, I admit,
我想请你回答我几个问题
I would like you to answer a few questions for me.
但问题可以待会再说
But it can wait.
我相信你也有问题要问我
I'm sure you have some questions for me, too.
是的，我不会再等了
I have, and I won't wait.
你为什么在做决策的过程中回避我？
Why did you avoid me in some decisions?
是的，是我的错
It's true. My mistake.
我这样做是因为我听说你
I did it because I heard that your views
对德国新政府的看法大多是负面的
on the new German government were mostly negative.
玛丽亚夫人，我从不隐瞒我的观点
Mrs. Maria, I never hid my views.
所有关于高等种族和低等种族的说法
All the stories about higher and lower races
对我来说都是毫无意义
are nonsense to me.
且非常危险的废话
Very dangerous nonsense.
- 但这并不意味着我... - 玛雅！
- But it doesn't mean that I... - Maya!
今晚应该会很美好
This should be a nice evening.
这世上没有高低种族
There are no higher and lower races.
只有特别的人
There are only exceptional people.
元首意识到了这一点
And the Fuhrer is aware of that.
我和你一样都是克罗地亚人
I'm a Croat as much as you are,
你也和我一样是塞尔维亚人
as you should be a Serb as much as I am.
这无关紧要
That doesn't matter.
但特殊性很重要
Exceptionality matters.
你在各方面都很特别
And you are exceptional... In every way.
你真的认为..
You really think that...
你肯定比你那个听话的
You're certainly more exceptional than your German husband
德国丈夫更特别
who dances to your tune.
杰出的女人总是比
Exceptional women are always more
杰出的男人更杰出
exceptional than exceptional men.
记住这一点
Remember that.
不管怎样..
Anyway...
你在跟我调情吗？
Are you flirting with me?
你觉得呢？
What do you think?
我第一眼见到你的时候，我就想要这个
I've wanted this since I saw you.
我给你带了点白兰地
I brought you some of my brandy.
谢谢
Thanks.
你也相信我是杀人犯吗？
Do you believe I'm a killer, too?
我不信
I don't.
我是少数人之一
I'm one of the few.
但是你想欺骗那些贫民窟的穷人
But you wanted to trick those poor people from Yataghan slum
很不幸被我知道了
and I know that, unfortunately.
无论我说什么都不是借口
Whatever I tell you is no excuse.
如果有上帝的话，会为此审判你的
God will judge you for that, if there is one.
但如果我不能证明你不是杀人犯
But if I fail to prove that you're not a murderer,
恐怕你很快就会见到上帝了
I'm afraid you'll meet God much sooner
比你想象的要快很多
than you could have imagined.
别费心了，都结束了
Don't bother, it's over.
还没有结束
It's not over.
迪米特里耶维奇，你一生中做过各种各样的事情..
Dimitriyevich, you've done various things in life...
但你是个好人
But you are a good man.
你帮助了很多人
You've helped so many people,
人们欣赏你...你并不孤单
people appreciate you... You're not alone.
我是你的朋友...
I'm your friend...
我会帮你的
And I'll help you.
你想要什么？
What do you want?
我要你告诉我
I want you to tell me
谁给你设的套？
who set this up for you?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
我救了你儿子
I saved your son.
他和我在一起很安全
He's with me. Safe.
- 你发誓! - 我发誓
- Swear! - I swear.
以你爱的人发誓
Swear on your loved ones.
我以索尼娅的坟墓起誓
I swear on Sonya's grave.
奥布拉德 · 萨夫科维奇
Obrad Savkovich.
是他拉我下水的
He got me involved in this.
我为了筹集我儿子的学费
I tricked people for the money he promised to give me
欺骗了贫民窟的人，但他一直没有给我钱
for my son's tuition and he never gave it to me.
是他害我被逮捕
He sent me here, to get arrested.
他是这一切的幕后黑手
He is behind everything.
我可以发誓他要为所有的谋杀负责
I could swear that he's responsible for all the murders.
既然我告诉了你..
Now that I told you this...
找到他
Find him.
杀了他
Kill him.
- 送小姐走吧 - 谢谢
- See the miss off. - Thank you.
我会尽我所能帮助你的
I'm here for everything I can help you with.
- 晚安 - 晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
打扰一下，萨夫科维奇先生，有位先生找你
Excuse me, Mr. Savkovich! The gentleman is on the phone.
我告诉过你不要打电话给我！
I told you not to call me!
什么？什么时候？
What?! When?
我们不能让这种事情发生
We can't let that happen.
尽快把他处理掉
Get rid of him, as soon as possible.
我不管这有多危险！
I don't care how risky it is!
照做就是！
Just do it!
奇妙的幻觉世界
MAGIC LILLY WONDERFUL WORLD OF ILLUSION